{"question":"32 + 80 = ","id":"0","answer":"112","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"3 + 56 = ","id":"1","answer":"59","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"9 + 50 = ","id":"2","answer":"59","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"17 + 78 = ","id":"3","answer":"95","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"36 + 91 = ","id":"4","answer":"127","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"70 + 73 = ","id":"5","answer":"143","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"35 + 21 = ","id":"6","answer":"56","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"77 + 24 = ","id":"7","answer":"101","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"69 + 60 = ","id":"8","answer":"129","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"84 + 83 = ","id":"9","answer":"167","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"73 + 33 = ","id":"10","answer":"106","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"82 + 6 = ","id":"11","answer":"88","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"46 + 43 = ","id":"12","answer":"89","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"12 + 42 = ","id":"13","answer":"54","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"15 + 56 = ","id":"14","answer":"71","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"21 + 54 = ","id":"15","answer":"75","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"47 + 27 = ","id":"16","answer":"74","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"80 + 90 = ","id":"17","answer":"170","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"52 + 70 = ","id":"18","answer":"122","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"2 + 96 = ","id":"19","answer":"98","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"51 + 35 = ","id":"20","answer":"86","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"28 + 8 = ","id":"21","answer":"36","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"67 + 63 = ","id":"22","answer":"130","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"81 + 87 = ","id":"23","answer":"168","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"8 + 51 = ","id":"24","answer":"59","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"12 + 20 = ","id":"25","answer":"32","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"78 + 53 = ","id":"26","answer":"131","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"63 + 58 = ","id":"27","answer":"121","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"52 + 41 = ","id":"28","answer":"93","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"96 + 28 = ","id":"29","answer":"124","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"44 + 32 = ","id":"30","answer":"76","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"50 + 66 = ","id":"31","answer":"116","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"8 + 83 = ","id":"32","answer":"91","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"53 + 85 = ","id":"33","answer":"138","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"83 + 66 = ","id":"34","answer":"149","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"51 + 74 = ","id":"35","answer":"125","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"50 + 31 = ","id":"36","answer":"81","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"97 + 51 = ","id":"37","answer":"148","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"96 + 68 = ","id":"38","answer":"164","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"85 + 24 = ","id":"39","answer":"109","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"6 + 81 = ","id":"40","answer":"87","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"74 + 98 = ","id":"41","answer":"172","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"79 + 37 = ","id":"42","answer":"116","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"39 + 66 = ","id":"43","answer":"105","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"26 + 1 = ","id":"44","answer":"27","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"7 + 37 = ","id":"45","answer":"44","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"81 + 53 = ","id":"46","answer":"134","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"74 + 44 = ","id":"47","answer":"118","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"49 + 60 = ","id":"48","answer":"109","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"85 + 100 = ","id":"49","answer":"185","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"27 + 27 = ","id":"50","answer":"54","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"66 + 75 = ","id":"51","answer":"141","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"38 + 54 = ","id":"52","answer":"92","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"1 + 94 = ","id":"53","answer":"95","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"13 + 82 = ","id":"54","answer":"95","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"47 + 54 = ","id":"55","answer":"101","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"84 + 20 = ","id":"56","answer":"104","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"23 + 11 = ","id":"57","answer":"34","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"61 + 9 = ","id":"58","answer":"70","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"80 + 82 = ","id":"59","answer":"162","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"70 + 90 = ","id":"60","answer":"160","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"28 + 65 = ","id":"61","answer":"93","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"71 + 4 = ","id":"62","answer":"75","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"64 + 94 = ","id":"63","answer":"158","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"68 + 8 = ","id":"64","answer":"76","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"31 + 76 = ","id":"65","answer":"107","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"10 + 100 = ","id":"66","answer":"110","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"87 + 29 = ","id":"67","answer":"116","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"5 + 46 = ","id":"68","answer":"51","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"9 + 35 = ","id":"69","answer":"44","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"44 + 39 = ","id":"70","answer":"83","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"36 + 97 = ","id":"71","answer":"133","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"12 + 52 = ","id":"72","answer":"64","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"80 + 31 = ","id":"73","answer":"111","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"75 + 64 = ","id":"74","answer":"139","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"59 + 85 = ","id":"75","answer":"144","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"58 + 43 = ","id":"76","answer":"101","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"0 + 88 = ","id":"77","answer":"88","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"53 + 0 = ","id":"78","answer":"53","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"27 + 55 = ","id":"79","answer":"82","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"12 + 25 = ","id":"80","answer":"37","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"89 + 74 = ","id":"81","answer":"163","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"96 + 76 = ","id":"82","answer":"172","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"41 + 6 = ","id":"83","answer":"47","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"14 + 84 = ","id":"84","answer":"98","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"80 + 78 = ","id":"85","answer":"158","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"87 + 96 = ","id":"86","answer":"183","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"87 + 97 = ","id":"87","answer":"184","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"16 + 95 = ","id":"88","answer":"111","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"84 + 49 = ","id":"89","answer":"133","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"81 + 66 = ","id":"90","answer":"147","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"23 + 56 = ","id":"91","answer":"79","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"43 + 51 = ","id":"92","answer":"94","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"94 + 62 = ","id":"93","answer":"156","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"22 + 35 = ","id":"94","answer":"57","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"70 + 39 = ","id":"95","answer":"109","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"85 + 89 = ","id":"96","answer":"174","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"59 + 35 = ","id":"97","answer":"94","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"34 + 3 = ","id":"98","answer":"37","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"15 + 1 = ","id":"99","answer":"16","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"addition"}
{"question":"11 - 68 = ","id":"100","answer":"-57","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"37 - 40 = ","id":"101","answer":"-3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"72 - 7 = ","id":"102","answer":"65","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"78 - 70 = ","id":"103","answer":"8","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"83 - 50 = ","id":"104","answer":"33","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"74 - 54 = ","id":"105","answer":"20","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"23 - 81 = ","id":"106","answer":"-58","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"76 - 82 = ","id":"107","answer":"-6","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"74 - 55 = ","id":"108","answer":"19","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"89 - 55 = ","id":"109","answer":"34","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"99 - 71 = ","id":"110","answer":"28","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"94 - 88 = ","id":"111","answer":"6","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"68 - 15 = ","id":"112","answer":"53","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"50 - 70 = ","id":"113","answer":"-20","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"59 - 28 = ","id":"114","answer":"31","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"54 - 49 = ","id":"115","answer":"5","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"63 - 42 = ","id":"116","answer":"21","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"76 - 2 = ","id":"117","answer":"74","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"61 - 16 = ","id":"118","answer":"45","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"35 - 76 = ","id":"119","answer":"-41","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"6 - 74 = ","id":"120","answer":"-68","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"4 - 26 = ","id":"121","answer":"-22","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"22 - 23 = ","id":"122","answer":"-1","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"83 - 80 = ","id":"123","answer":"3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"100 - 1 = ","id":"124","answer":"99","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"35 - 38 = ","id":"125","answer":"-3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"6 - 48 = ","id":"126","answer":"-42","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"87 - 50 = ","id":"127","answer":"37","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"91 - 61 = ","id":"128","answer":"30","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"87 - 49 = ","id":"129","answer":"38","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"81 - 63 = ","id":"130","answer":"18","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"18 - 28 = ","id":"131","answer":"-10","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"85 - 74 = ","id":"132","answer":"11","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"56 - 76 = ","id":"133","answer":"-20","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"63 - 8 = ","id":"134","answer":"55","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"61 - 73 = ","id":"135","answer":"-12","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"68 - 65 = ","id":"136","answer":"3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"99 - 28 = ","id":"137","answer":"71","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"11 - 51 = ","id":"138","answer":"-40","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"93 - 96 = ","id":"139","answer":"-3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"0 - 82 = ","id":"140","answer":"-82","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"42 - 71 = ","id":"141","answer":"-29","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"72 - 91 = ","id":"142","answer":"-19","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"85 - 68 = ","id":"143","answer":"17","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"78 - 10 = ","id":"144","answer":"68","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"53 - 13 = ","id":"145","answer":"40","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"48 - 100 = ","id":"146","answer":"-52","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"94 - 97 = ","id":"147","answer":"-3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"96 - 81 = ","id":"148","answer":"15","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"40 - 89 = ","id":"149","answer":"-49","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"97 - 17 = ","id":"150","answer":"80","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"88 - 28 = ","id":"151","answer":"60","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"57 - 34 = ","id":"152","answer":"23","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"19 - 57 = ","id":"153","answer":"-38","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"93 - 56 = ","id":"154","answer":"37","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"43 - 69 = ","id":"155","answer":"-26","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"1 - 26 = ","id":"156","answer":"-25","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"44 - 60 = ","id":"157","answer":"-16","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"67 - 34 = ","id":"158","answer":"33","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"33 - 17 = ","id":"159","answer":"16","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"46 - 90 = ","id":"160","answer":"-44","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"73 - 26 = ","id":"161","answer":"47","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"7 - 49 = ","id":"162","answer":"-42","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"62 - 91 = ","id":"163","answer":"-29","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"44 - 81 = ","id":"164","answer":"-37","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"79 - 57 = ","id":"165","answer":"22","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"17 - 43 = ","id":"166","answer":"-26","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"44 - 40 = ","id":"167","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"100 - 17 = ","id":"168","answer":"83","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"92 - 97 = ","id":"169","answer":"-5","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"26 - 46 = ","id":"170","answer":"-20","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"50 - 37 = ","id":"171","answer":"13","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"79 - 7 = ","id":"172","answer":"72","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"57 - 71 = ","id":"173","answer":"-14","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"58 - 34 = ","id":"174","answer":"24","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"21 - 87 = ","id":"175","answer":"-66","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"10 - 46 = ","id":"176","answer":"-36","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"20 - 65 = ","id":"177","answer":"-45","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"60 - 49 = ","id":"178","answer":"11","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"35 - 92 = ","id":"179","answer":"-57","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"71 - 54 = ","id":"180","answer":"17","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"10 - 8 = ","id":"181","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"93 - 23 = ","id":"182","answer":"70","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"39 - 12 = ","id":"183","answer":"27","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"66 - 43 = ","id":"184","answer":"23","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"21 - 17 = ","id":"185","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"31 - 89 = ","id":"186","answer":"-58","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"62 - 82 = ","id":"187","answer":"-20","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"21 - 34 = ","id":"188","answer":"-13","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"94 - 18 = ","id":"189","answer":"76","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"33 - 50 = ","id":"190","answer":"-17","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"46 - 52 = ","id":"191","answer":"-6","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"28 - 14 = ","id":"192","answer":"14","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"85 - 82 = ","id":"193","answer":"3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"11 - 48 = ","id":"194","answer":"-37","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"30 - 96 = ","id":"195","answer":"-66","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"75 - 1 = ","id":"196","answer":"74","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"27 - 10 = ","id":"197","answer":"17","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"83 - 88 = ","id":"198","answer":"-5","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"65 - 27 = ","id":"199","answer":"38","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"subtraction"}
{"question":"3 * 17 = ","id":"200","answer":"51","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"18 * 14 = ","id":"201","answer":"252","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"9 * 4 = ","id":"202","answer":"36","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"1 * 10 = ","id":"203","answer":"10","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"15 * 8 = ","id":"204","answer":"120","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"15 * 14 = ","id":"205","answer":"210","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"17 * 11 = ","id":"206","answer":"187","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"20 * 6 = ","id":"207","answer":"120","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"1 * 5 = ","id":"208","answer":"5","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"8 * 4 = ","id":"209","answer":"32","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"9 * 9 = ","id":"210","answer":"81","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"18 * 17 = ","id":"211","answer":"306","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"16 * 10 = ","id":"212","answer":"160","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"12 * 3 = ","id":"213","answer":"36","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"4 * 2 = ","id":"214","answer":"8","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"3 * 14 = ","id":"215","answer":"42","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"5 * 2 = ","id":"216","answer":"10","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"12 * 6 = ","id":"217","answer":"72","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"10 * 14 = ","id":"218","answer":"140","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"6 * 18 = ","id":"219","answer":"108","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"17 * 4 = ","id":"220","answer":"68","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"3 * 18 = ","id":"221","answer":"54","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"8 * 9 = ","id":"222","answer":"72","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"7 * 11 = ","id":"223","answer":"77","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"7 * 7 = ","id":"224","answer":"49","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"18 * 4 = ","id":"225","answer":"72","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"10 * 12 = ","id":"226","answer":"120","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"19 * 1 = ","id":"227","answer":"19","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"15 * 5 = ","id":"228","answer":"75","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"20 * 19 = ","id":"229","answer":"380","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"4 * 1 = ","id":"230","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"11 * 20 = ","id":"231","answer":"220","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"14 * 5 = ","id":"232","answer":"70","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"18 * 15 = ","id":"233","answer":"270","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"2 * 11 = ","id":"234","answer":"22","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"15 * 19 = ","id":"235","answer":"285","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"17 * 8 = ","id":"236","answer":"136","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"17 * 13 = ","id":"237","answer":"221","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"5 * 18 = ","id":"238","answer":"90","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"15 * 7 = ","id":"239","answer":"105","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"7 * 5 = ","id":"240","answer":"35","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"6 * 8 = ","id":"241","answer":"48","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"3 * 6 = ","id":"242","answer":"18","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"6 * 13 = ","id":"243","answer":"78","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"1 * 16 = ","id":"244","answer":"16","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"12 * 18 = ","id":"245","answer":"216","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"9 * 5 = ","id":"246","answer":"45","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"14 * 16 = ","id":"247","answer":"224","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"11 * 12 = ","id":"248","answer":"132","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"18 * 10 = ","id":"249","answer":"180","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"20 * 4 = ","id":"250","answer":"80","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"7 * 18 = ","id":"251","answer":"126","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"5 * 4 = ","id":"252","answer":"20","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"15 * 11 = ","id":"253","answer":"165","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"17 * 5 = ","id":"254","answer":"85","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"7 * 3 = ","id":"255","answer":"21","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"19 * 11 = ","id":"256","answer":"209","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"18 * 16 = ","id":"257","answer":"288","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"2 * 17 = ","id":"258","answer":"34","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"12 * 17 = ","id":"259","answer":"204","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"4 * 13 = ","id":"260","answer":"52","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"3 * 13 = ","id":"261","answer":"39","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"10 * 11 = ","id":"262","answer":"110","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"12 * 12 = ","id":"263","answer":"144","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"14 * 12 = ","id":"264","answer":"168","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"17 * 19 = ","id":"265","answer":"323","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"15 * 9 = ","id":"266","answer":"135","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"6 * 19 = ","id":"267","answer":"114","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"14 * 19 = ","id":"268","answer":"266","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"4 * 7 = ","id":"269","answer":"28","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"12 * 20 = ","id":"270","answer":"240","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"9 * 19 = ","id":"271","answer":"171","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"10 * 8 = ","id":"272","answer":"80","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"3 * 20 = ","id":"273","answer":"60","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"2 * 7 = ","id":"274","answer":"14","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"16 * 15 = ","id":"275","answer":"240","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"12 * 7 = ","id":"276","answer":"84","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"6 * 17 = ","id":"277","answer":"102","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"10 * 9 = ","id":"278","answer":"90","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"10 * 20 = ","id":"279","answer":"200","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"14 * 13 = ","id":"280","answer":"182","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"16 * 12 = ","id":"281","answer":"192","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"8 * 5 = ","id":"282","answer":"40","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"8 * 20 = ","id":"283","answer":"160","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"18 * 2 = ","id":"284","answer":"36","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"13 * 15 = ","id":"285","answer":"195","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"15 * 17 = ","id":"286","answer":"255","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"3 * 3 = ","id":"287","answer":"9","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"10 * 10 = ","id":"288","answer":"100","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"20 * 13 = ","id":"289","answer":"260","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"20 * 20 = ","id":"290","answer":"400","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"14 * 11 = ","id":"291","answer":"154","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"19 * 12 = ","id":"292","answer":"228","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"18 * 20 = ","id":"293","answer":"360","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"20 * 14 = ","id":"294","answer":"280","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"13 * 11 = ","id":"295","answer":"143","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"2 * 19 = ","id":"296","answer":"38","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"20 * 5 = ","id":"297","answer":"100","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"6 * 9 = ","id":"298","answer":"54","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"10 * 7 = ","id":"299","answer":"70","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"multiplication"}
{"question":"84 / 2 = ","id":"300","answer":"42","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"54 / 6 = ","id":"301","answer":"9","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"8 / 2 = ","id":"302","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"69 / 23 = ","id":"303","answer":"3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"24 / 8 = ","id":"304","answer":"3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"72 / 4 = ","id":"305","answer":"18","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"35 / 7 = ","id":"306","answer":"5","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"62 / 2 = ","id":"307","answer":"31","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"24 / 4 = ","id":"308","answer":"6","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"78 / 2 = ","id":"309","answer":"39","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"32 / 2 = ","id":"310","answer":"16","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"60 / 15 = ","id":"311","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"6 / 3 = ","id":"312","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"76 / 38 = ","id":"313","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"32 / 16 = ","id":"314","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"46 / 23 = ","id":"315","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"55 / 5 = ","id":"316","answer":"11","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"60 / 5 = ","id":"317","answer":"12","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"75 / 5 = ","id":"318","answer":"15","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"34 / 2 = ","id":"319","answer":"17","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"28 / 4 = ","id":"320","answer":"7","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"30 / 15 = ","id":"321","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"30 / 2 = ","id":"322","answer":"15","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"12 / 6 = ","id":"323","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"72 / 36 = ","id":"324","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"60 / 6 = ","id":"325","answer":"10","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"48 / 3 = ","id":"326","answer":"16","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"27 / 3 = ","id":"327","answer":"9","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"33 / 11 = ","id":"328","answer":"3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"99 / 33 = ","id":"329","answer":"3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"98 / 2 = ","id":"330","answer":"49","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"76 / 2 = ","id":"331","answer":"38","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"100 / 2 = ","id":"332","answer":"50","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"69 / 3 = ","id":"333","answer":"23","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"42 / 21 = ","id":"334","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"90 / 3 = ","id":"335","answer":"30","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"36 / 4 = ","id":"336","answer":"9","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"54 / 2 = ","id":"337","answer":"27","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"60 / 10 = ","id":"338","answer":"6","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"78 / 39 = ","id":"339","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"56 / 7 = ","id":"340","answer":"8","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"20 / 2 = ","id":"341","answer":"10","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"60 / 4 = ","id":"342","answer":"15","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"10 / 5 = ","id":"343","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"99 / 3 = ","id":"344","answer":"33","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"32 / 8 = ","id":"345","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"70 / 14 = ","id":"346","answer":"5","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"52 / 26 = ","id":"347","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"82 / 2 = ","id":"348","answer":"41","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"96 / 2 = ","id":"349","answer":"48","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"12 / 2 = ","id":"350","answer":"6","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"84 / 42 = ","id":"351","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"80 / 8 = ","id":"352","answer":"10","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"80 / 16 = ","id":"353","answer":"5","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"86 / 43 = ","id":"354","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"63 / 3 = ","id":"355","answer":"21","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"84 / 3 = ","id":"356","answer":"28","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"70 / 5 = ","id":"357","answer":"14","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"51 / 17 = ","id":"358","answer":"3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"28 / 2 = ","id":"359","answer":"14","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"64 / 4 = ","id":"360","answer":"16","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"45 / 15 = ","id":"361","answer":"3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"35 / 5 = ","id":"362","answer":"7","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"93 / 31 = ","id":"363","answer":"3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"99 / 9 = ","id":"364","answer":"11","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"72 / 3 = ","id":"365","answer":"24","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"60 / 3 = ","id":"366","answer":"20","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"94 / 47 = ","id":"367","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"44 / 4 = ","id":"368","answer":"11","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"76 / 4 = ","id":"369","answer":"19","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"36 / 18 = ","id":"370","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"88 / 11 = ","id":"371","answer":"8","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"84 / 6 = ","id":"372","answer":"14","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"94 / 2 = ","id":"373","answer":"47","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"77 / 7 = ","id":"374","answer":"11","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"98 / 7 = ","id":"375","answer":"14","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"42 / 7 = ","id":"376","answer":"6","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"78 / 3 = ","id":"377","answer":"26","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"96 / 24 = ","id":"378","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"98 / 14 = ","id":"379","answer":"7","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"54 / 27 = ","id":"380","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"42 / 14 = ","id":"381","answer":"3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"12 / 3 = ","id":"382","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"68 / 34 = ","id":"383","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"48 / 6 = ","id":"384","answer":"8","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"88 / 8 = ","id":"385","answer":"11","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"68 / 17 = ","id":"386","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"90 / 10 = ","id":"387","answer":"9","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"62 / 31 = ","id":"388","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"74 / 37 = ","id":"389","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"4 / 2 = ","id":"390","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"87 / 29 = ","id":"391","answer":"3","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"28 / 14 = ","id":"392","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"70 / 2 = ","id":"393","answer":"35","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"22 / 11 = ","id":"394","answer":"2","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"80 / 5 = ","id":"395","answer":"16","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"70 / 10 = ","id":"396","answer":"7","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"92 / 23 = ","id":"397","answer":"4","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"60 / 2 = ","id":"398","answer":"30","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
{"question":"72 / 8 = ","id":"399","answer":"9","category_id":"math","sub_cat_id":"arithmetic","topic_id":"division"}
